I've already
implemented my tactics.
What?!
Okuyasu's brother almost
did me in back there.
Koichi, I think it's time
we hightail it out of here.
Huh?
But what about the bow and
arrow that got me?
The bow and arrow?
Okuyasu's brother must've
hid it somewhere.
Don't tell me you…?
Yes…
Don't forget…
They said their dad's
around here somewhere.
Look, I'm hurt pretty bad.
Let's just leave it be for now.
W-We can't do that!
I-I'm alive today cause
you healed my wounds, but…
If someone else is shot
with that bow and arrow,
they won't be so lucky!
Another will die in Morioh!
You can stay here.
I can go find it by myself!
Besides, I don't think
their dad is in this house anymore.
I-If he was,
he would've come out by now.
He doesn't look it,
but he's got a helluva lot of guts.
At least when
the going gets tough…
Or when he's not thinking.
Whatever the case,
we better get
the hell out of this place fast.
Hey…
W-What?
You're not stopping me.
I'm not.
We're gonna snap that
bow and arrow in two,
then say goodbye to
this dump together,
Koichi.
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 5
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 3
There's an attic.
The bow and arrow's
probably up here.
Th-There it is!
The bow and arrow!
It's on the wall back there!
Hey, this doesn't sound good.
Something's in there.
Something
chained up in there?
Maybe it's a dog?
That's definitely not
a person in there…
It sounds like
some kind of animal.
This is really scary!
What do we do now?!
What do we do now?
This was all your idea!
I know, but…
We can't go back now.
All right, Koichi.
On the count of three,
you bust the door open.
That should scare it.
Then I'll run over and break
the bow and arrow in half.
Got it?
Yeah.
Let's do this.
One…
Two…
Three!
What the hell?!
Koichi!
Help!
That's no Stand.
That's a real hand!
That's a real arm!
H-Help me!
Gross…
I wasn't trying to sever it…
Wh-What the heck was that?
To think it's been living
in my own backyard…
Gah…
So you finally saw him…
You were never
supposed to see him!
You again…
You're looking at…
our father.
And Dad needs these.
Th-The bow and arrow…
I must find more Stand users
for Dad.
That's why I'll never
let anyone have them.
I'll protect them forever!
Did some disease
do this to him?
A disease?
Not even close.
Dad's in excellent health,
with a hearty appetite.
All he does is moan.
You can bet he has
no awareness I'm his son.
So you've been searching for
a Stand user
who can cure your father.
Cure?
You mean you cure him?
Wrong again, I'm afraid.
Completely wrong!
I've been searching for
a Stand user who'll kill Dad.
Dad won't die.
He can't die!
I could bash his head in,
chop him into tiny pieces,
slice him to ribbons,
and he'd never die!
He deserves the right to die.
I swore, ever since I was a child,
I'd do anything to give him that.
To do that,
I need the bow and arrow.
Without it, Dad will go on
like this for all eternity.
All because some bastard named
DIO decided to implant his cells
inside his skull and turn him
into a monster!
DIO?
Did you say DIO?
That the same guy
Mr. Jotaro was talking about?
Let me tell you a bit
about what used to be,
Josuke Higashikata.
What I'm about to tell you
isn't completely unrelated to your life.
It all started eleven years ago,
in 1988.
I was seven,
Okuyasu was four.
We were living in Tokyo.
It was the middle of
the Bubble Economy,
and spirits were high,
except my father's.
Mom grew sick and died,
and Dad's business
went under.
LUXURY CONDOMINIUMS
NIJIMURA PROPERTIES CO.
He was buried under
a mountain of debt.
He'd often beat us
for no apparent reason.
Dad was
the consummate loser.
Then, suddenly,
seemingly endless wads of cash
started rolling in.
There were even jewels
and precious metals.
But Dad didn't have a job.
It was only later, after
some research, that I found out.
My own father had sold
his soul to DIO.
He became one of his lackeys
for monetary gain.
Apparently DIO was scouring
the globe for potential Stand users.
Somehow, he figured out
Dad was Stand-capable,
though, to this day, I have no idea
what his Stand is.
Then one day…
It was ten years ago,
but I remember it
like it was yesterday.
It was 2 in the afternoon,
and I'd just come home
from school…
Okuyasu!
Did he hit you again?
That bastard!
N-No!
Huh?
DIO…
DIO's died…
That must be the reason!
Dad?
Dad, I'll Callan ambulance.
It's no use! I'm not sick!
The flesh bud's
ravaging my body!
— This is the end!
— Dad!
In the span of one year,
he had lost his ability
to recognize us,
and had become a
muttering glob of flesh!
DIO implanted his own cells into
the minds of those he distrusted,
enabling him to manipulate
his victims at will.
DIO implanted
one of those things in Dad!
For ten years I threw myself
into research.
I studied Stands,
I learned about Jotaro…
Then I learned of
Enyaba the hag,
and got a hold of
the bow and arrow.
But in the process,
I resigned myself to
the fact that
Dad would never recover.
He had become one with
DIO's immortal cells.
He spends his days
doing nothing but this.
Every cursed day…
Every moment of every day,
for the past ten years,
he's desperately scratched
around that box of rubbish.
Dare I confiscate the box,
he wails and groans for days.
I'm sick of it all!
I look at him,
and I become disgusted with
the idea of life itself.
I've told you over and over,
stop making this blasted mess!
When I discipline him,
the bastard seems to hear me!
Yet the rummaging
continues…
The wretched swine
can't help himself!
Bleh…
Hey! The only one who needs
to stop is you!
He's still your father!
In a way you're right.
He is my father…
my blood.
But the father I see
before me isn't the father I know.
This man sold
his soul to DIO.
This man is living
the life he created!
At the same time,
seeing my own father like
this is unbearable.
Do you have any idea
how this feels?
That's why I want to give him
the chance to die.
With him dead,
I'll finally be able to live again!
Goddammit!
I told you to stop!
I'm sick of all this!
Hey!
That's enough!
Sorry, but I can't let
you have this bow and arrow.
Not now, not ever!
You seem to be mistaken!
I'll get the bow and arrow later.
My sights are on that box!
Th-The box?
The way he's been
clutching those scraps of paper,
there's something there.
It all makes sense now.
A family photo…
He knew what he was doing.
For ten years
he had a purpose.
He was looking for the photo
of his sons when they were young.
He may not be
completely aware,
but deep down in his heart,
he has his memories!
Memories of
a time long past!
THE HAND
If you can give up on
a Stand that kills,
in favor of a
Stand that heals,
then I'm willing to help.
But you'll have to hand over
that bow and arrow.
I'm gonna break 'em in two.
Planning on running?
Bro, please,
stop this.
Okuyasu!
Come on, let's just put
an end to all this, okay?
So you were here…
There's a chance
Dad could get better, right?
So what if he doesn't look
like he used to.
He could have his soul back,
his memories.
Right?
Okuyasu! What do you think
you're doing?
Bro…
Out of my way, Okuyasu!
No matter what happens,
I can never turn back!
With this very
bow and arrow,
I've already slaughtered
countless people in this town!
Besides, to me,
you're no longer my brother!
You're no longer my brother,
which is why I can kill you
without a second thought!
Bro…
Quick question…
Anyone else in your family
besides you two and your dad?
Anyone else?
It's just the three of us.
Th-That's…
It's coming from the outlet…
Okuyasu!
Pull your head out of your ass,
you idiot!
Bro!
I'll be taking this bow and
arrow, Keicho Nijimura!
Remember me?
You were kind enough
to shoot me with this arrow
and awaken my Stand!
You…
You think you can handle
this bow and arrow?
Keicho Nijimura!
You said Stands are a
manifestation of the soul, correct?
Well, I've matured!
Or did you not expect my Stand,
Chili Pepper,
to have come this far?
Worse Company!
Stop talking!
Th-That's…
Electricity!
Okuyasu's brother's turning
into electricity!
And so is
the bow and arrow!
Bro!
Get away from me!
You'll be pulled in, too!
Bro…
S-Shit!
He's taking
the bow and arrow!
Okuyasu…
You… You've always
held me back!
Bro!
Josuke!
Without a doubt a Stand user
was pee ring in
from that window
That Stand back there…
do you know it, Okuyasu?
N-No. Bro didn't tell me about
a lot of the Stand users he found.
J-Josuke!
Th-That's…
Okuyasu…
Bro…
it was only a matter of time.
I knew he'd do
bad things with his life.
It was his fate.
But…
But in the end, Bro…
My brother, in the end,
at the very last second,
he saved me,
didn't he?
Josuke,
you saw it, right?
Yeah.
Without a doubt.
Your brother
saved your life.
Is this Jotaro Kujo?
I don't recognize your voice.
Who is this?
Who I am doesn't matter.
Jotaro Kujo,
I'm asking you kindly
to get the hell out of Morioh.
Let me see
if I've got this straight,
a complete stranger wants me
to leave town for no particular reason.
If you were me,
would you get up and leave?
I have the bow and arrow
I took it…
after I killed Keicho Nijimura.
And I don't mind
getting rid of you either.
You know I've heard Jotaro…
you have the ability to stop
time for one or two seconds.
But since you're
such a tough guy,
I thought I'd try to convince
you over the phone first.
Are you a Stand user too?
What do you want
with the bow and arrow?
I don't mean to
cause you any trouble.
NUMBER WITHHELD PUBLIC PHONE
As long as Josuke Higashikata
minds his own business,
I won't lay
a finger on him, either.
I just received
this Stand ability.
All I want is
to have a little fun.
I've had enough
entrance exams and resumes.
So you're a student?
What the hell difference
does that make?!
Listen! If you wear out
your welcome in my town,
I'll kill both you and Josuke!
Got it?!
How many other Stand users
are in this—
Good grief…
Keicho Nijimura was buried
in Kunimi Peak Cemetery,
west of Morioh.
The bow and arrow
remains missing.
NIJIMURA FAMILY
For Okuyasu Nijimura,
it was time
to keep his father company
for a while.
And..
Josuke, can you get that?
Okay…
Hey, Josuke!
It's time to go to school!
Huh?
Starting today, I'm gonna be
going to the same school as you!
That doesn't mean you
have to come and get me!
This isn't
elementary school!
Wow, I never knew your house
and my house were so close!
Well, that is a surprise…
Come on!
Let's go!
Oh, so you're
Josuke's friend?
Hi!
I'm Okuyasu Nijimura!
Come in and have some coffee
while he gets ready.
Really?
Don't mind if I do, then!
You know,
your mom is really pretty.
I'll be right there!
Well, this is just great…
What'd I get myself into with this guy…?
EPISODE 6
KOICHI HIROSE (REVERB)